Guide to the Bobbye S. Ortiz Papers, 1919-1993 and undated (bulk 1950-1990) RL.00978
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Phonograph Records Series, [195-]-[198-] and undated
  - Twelve Inch Recordings
    - Cuba (Box 40)
      - #50 Title: Rabo de Nube Vol. 1
        - Performer: Silvio Rodriguez (Box 40)
          Side 2: Que ya vivi que te vas, Con diex aos de menos, Imaginate, Testamento
          Record Label: EGREM, LD 3844
      - #51 Title: Cuba que linda es Cuba
        - Performer: Orfeon Santiago, Orquesta EGREM, Conjunto Palmas y Caas, Armando Pico, Coro I.C.R., Banda Nacional de Conciertas (Box 40)
          Side 1: Cuba, que linda es Cuba, La comparsa, Son de la loma
          Side 2: Siboney, Ay! Mama Ines, Lamento esclavo
          Record Label: EGREM Areito LDA-3313
      - #52 Title: Trio voces modernas
        - Performer: Trio Voces Modernas (Box 40)
          Side 1: Cancin de cuna despertar un negrito, Imprescindible, Te doy una cancin, Luna tucumana, Despertar, El son del Palmar
          Side 2: No ha ido la Habana, Encuentrame, Caminito del indio, Ojala, Embrujo, Cuidadito compay gallo
          Record Label: EGREM Areito, LD-3555
    - Dominican Republic
      - #53 Title: La hora est llegando! The Time Is Coming!
        - Performer: Expresin Joven (Voice of Youth), Los Macetongos (Box 40)
          Side 1: Abra las rejas, seor Gobierno; Casas de carton, Amor en la guerra, A desalambrar, Esta llegando la hora
          Side 2: No amigo, no vayas aun al sol; Pobre del cantor, Compadre del cantor, Compadre 'mon, Cancin antes del odio; Fransisco Alberto, Caramba!
          Record Label: Paredon Records, P-1025
      - #54 Title: De la loma al llano
        - Performer: Xiomara Fortuna (Box 40)
          Side 1: Quiero abrir una ventana, Mujer campesina, Tiempo oportuno, Gaga Lola, Ay si tuviera tierra!
          Side 2: Quisiera con mil amores, Muchacho hargan, Trabajo y mas trabajo, Tenemos que organizamos, Estoy unida
          Record Label: Mujeres en Desarrollo Dominicana (MUDE)
    - El Salvador
      - #55 Title: El Salvador libre
        - Performer: Roque Dalton (Box 40)
          Side 1: Taberno y otros lugares - Taberna, A muerte fiel, a muerte convivada, Los jvenes, La lucha de los contrarios, pero..., Decires, 50 Aniversario, Tu compaa
          Side 2: Historia de un amor - I Los orgenes, II Escrito en una servilleta, Cuando salgas luna llena, Tragedia no precisamente optimista, El ser social determina la conciencia social, La cabeza contra el muro, Revisionismo, Despus de la bomba atmica, Sobre dolores de cabeza, Al Salvador
          Record Label: B.C.R.D., L.D.-001
      - #56 Title: El Salvador: su canto, su lucha, su victoria, amaneciendo! El Salvador: Its Song, Struggle, Victory, Awakening!
        - Performer: Yolocamba Ita - La rebelda de la Siembra (The Planting of the Rebellion) (Box 40)
          Side 1: Poema de Amor, La Barricada, El Salvador T Venciendo, Regalo a un Nio, Marcha del EPL
          Side 2: A los Cados en 1932, El Miliciano, Con Farabundo y Romero, San Romero de Amrica
          Record Label: Peon Records, 001
    - France
      - #57 Title: Un soir a l'cluse
        - Performer: Agns Capri, Caroline Cler, Giani Esposito, Jacques Fabbri, Jacques Grello, Marc et Andr, Lo Nol, Brigitte Sabouraud, Cora Vaucaire (Box 40)
          Side 1: La Petite Servante, La voix du sang, Les pchs capitaux, La marchande de fleurs, La complainte de la jeune nonne contra son cœur, La chanson du pharmacien, Le souper chez Borgia
          Side 2: La complainte de Mackie, Plan de Paris, Dans la sciure, Un vieux boxeur, Les clowns, L'Amnsique, La chose aurait pu
          Record Label: Vega, V 30 S 800
      - #58 Title: Les journes de Mai 68 par las journalistes de R.T.L.
        - Performer: Jean-Pierre Farkas (Box 40)
          Side 1: De Gaulle s'exprime, Cohn-Bendit et la dmocratie directe, Cohn-Bendit vu par Georges Sguy, Fermeture de la Facult des Lettres de Nanterre par le doyen Grappin, Fermeture de la Sorbonne par le Recteur Roche, Les premires bagarres Boulevard Saint-Michel, Premires impressions d'Alain Peyrfitte, La Premire meute du Quartier Latin, Les tudiants l'Arc de Triomphe, Le Palais Bourbon l'Elyse: Commentaires des tudiants, Alain Peyrefitte promet d'ouvrir la Sorbonne, Les lycns entrent en action, La nuit des barricadas de la rue Guy Lussac: Dialogue Chalin-Geismar: Les premires barricadas: Les combates de la rue, Retour de Georges Pompidou, Grve gnrale et occupation de la Sorbonne, Jean-Paul Sartre et la violence
          Side 2: Occupation de Sud Aviation Bouguenas, Occupation de l'Odon, Occupation de l'Usine de Cleon, Porquoi ce mouvement spontan?: Par Eugene Descamps, Les tudiants chez Renault Billancourt, La "Chienlit", Occupation du Plazza Athenee, Pierre Mendes- France prend position, L'autogestion vue par la C.F.D.T., Monsieur Waldeck-Rochet l'Assemble Nationale, Monsieur Pisani votera la censure, Cohn-Bendit en Allemagne, La foule coute l'aanonce du rfrendum par le Gnral de Gaulle, La "prise" de la bourse, Nouvelle soire d'meutes au Quartier Latin, Franois Mitterand propose un gouvernement de transition, Flash de l'lyse: De Gaulle part pour Colombey les glises, Pierre Mendes et le gouvernement de transition, Allocution intgrale du Gnral de Gaulle, Michel Debr dans la foule des Champs-Elyses
          Record Label: Philips 77.757 L
      - #59 Title: Jean Ferrat
        - Performer: Jean Ferrat (Box 40)
          Side 1: Maria, Heureux celui qui meurt d'aimer, En groupe, en ligue, en procession, Si je mourais la-bas, La libert est en voyage
          Side 2: Un enfant quitte Paris, Un jour, un jour, Alleluia, Chanson pour toi, Pauvre Boris
          Record Label: Vendettes, XBLY 80 338
      - #60 Title: Jean Ferrat
        - Performer: Jean Ferrat (Box 40)
          Side 1: Cuba si, Mourir au soleil, Excusez-moi, Prisunic, A Santiago
          Side 2: Ce qu'on est bien mon amour, Les guerilleros, Au point du jour, Pauvres petits c., Indien
          Record Label: Vedettes, XBLY 80 360
      - #61 Title: La Bobina (Box 41)
        - Performer: Juliette Greco (Box 41)
          Side 1: In memoriam, La fte est finie, Paralllbipdes, Vieille, Madame Bovary, La propritaire
          Side 2: L'auberge, La Venus du ve Zouave, Lers quatre saisons "Je peux vous raconter", La Fiance du pirate de "L'Opra de quat'sous", Sur L'arbre mort, Olga
          Record Label: Philips, 77.814
      - #62 Title: Juliette
        - Performer: Juliette Greco (Box 41)
          Side 1: L'a Fte est l, Bonjour tristesse, Complainte du tlphone, Musique mchanique, La Valse des si, Qu'on est bien
          Side 2: Java partout, La marche nuptiale, La complainte, Chandernagor, Que j'aime, Les lunettes
          Record Label: Columbia, WL 138
      - #63 Title: L'Olympia
        - Performer: Juliette Greco (Box 41)
          Side 1: Introduction, J'ai le cœur aussi grand, Plus jamais, Un petit poisson, un petit oiseau, Vieille, Reveuse et fragile, A contrecœur, Je suis bien
          Side 2: Chambre 33, C'etait peut-etre, Nos cheres maisons, La fiance du pirate, Miracle a Seville, Jolie mome, Cimetieres militaires
          Record Label: Philips, 70.342
      - #64 Title: St. Germain des Prs
        - Performer: Juliette Greco (Box 41)
          Side 1: La belle vie, la belle toile, Les enfants qui s'aiment, Les feuilles mortes, Amours perdues, Je has les dimanches
          Side 2: Barbara-song, Pirate Jenny, Embrasse-moi, Sous le ciel de Paris, Je suis comme je suis, Je mens
          Record Label: Columbia, CL 569
      - #65 Title: Juliette Greco
        - Performer: Juliette Greco (Box 41)
          Side 1: Tu me dirais, Les cloches, Dieu est negre, Complainte de Sir Jack l'Eventreur, Si tu t'magines, Chanson pour L'Auvergnat, Les Croix
          Side 2: Ca va "Le Diable", Coin de rue, Les dames de la poste, L'Ombre
          Record Label: Columbia, ML 5088
      - #66 Title: L'Honneur des potes: Pomes publis sous l'Occupation Allemande par les Editions de Minuit (Box 41)
        Side 1: Prlude la Diane franaise, Ce cœur qui hassait la guerre, Paris-Pentecte, Refuge, Romance des 40.000, La patience, Les dents serres, Prire pour les Russes, Ballade de celui qui chanta dans les supplices
        Side 2: Courage, Le chle rouge-gorge, Police, Sonnet, Corruption, Lui, Les tra"tres se trahissent, Prface en prose, Les charniers, Le vent, Avis, Les armes de la douleur
        Record Label: Le Chant du Monde, LDX-S-6027
      - #67 Title: Lo paios que vol viure
        - Performer: Marti (Box 41)
          Side 1: Lo pais que vol viure, Montsegur, Un Pais, un poble, Lo soldat desconegut, Tornaras, Lo tamborinaire
          Side 2: Cridaraio, Perque m'an pas dit?, Ciutat de carcassona, Lengadoc roge, La longa marcha, Los corbasses
          Record Label: Le Chant du Monde, XVI 74502
      - #68 Title: Serge Reggiani
        - Performer: Serge Reggiani (Box 41)
          Side 1: Les loups sont entres dans Paris, La vie c'est comme une dent, Prlude de Sarah, Sarah, Maxim's, Ma solitude, Fleurs de meninges
          Side 2: Le petit garon, Prlude extrait de "Pater Noster", Quand j'aurai du vent dans mon crane, Ma liberte, Prlude extrait du "Pont Mirabeau", Paris ma rose, L'hotel des rendez-moi a, Prlude dormeur du Val, Le deserteur
          Record Label: Disques Jacques Canetti, LPL 1434
      - #69 Title: Serge Reggiani
        - Performer: Serge Reggiani (Box 41)
          Side 1: Rupture, L'absence, La putain, Comme elle est longue mourir ma jeunesse, Va-t'en savoir pourquoi
          Side 2: Ma fille, Dans ses yeux, L'italien, Edith, La conquantaine
          Record Label: Polydor, 2393 026
      - #70 Title: Chansons possibles, ou impossibles
        - Performer: Boris Vian (Box 41)
          Side 1: Les joyeux bouchers, Cinmatographe, Fais-moi mal Johnny, La java des bombes atomiques, Je bois, Juste le temps de vivre
          Side 2: Le dserteur, Le petit commerce, Je suis snob, La java martienne, Complainte du progres, On n'est pas la pour se faire eng, Bour de complexes
          Record Label: Philips, P 77.922
      - #71 Title: 20 ans dja
        - Performer: Claude Vinci (Box 41)
          Side 1: Le chant des partisans, Nuit et brouillard, L'affiche rouge, Liberte
          Side 2: a fera vingt ans, Vous reviendrez, Dans varsovie, Le chant des marais, Un accordon pour Paris, Au nom du front parfait profond, Rendez-vous avec la libert, Ballade du bonheur difficile
          Record Label: Philips Airs de France, 77.228
    - General
      - #72 Title: Typical Latin American melodies
        - Performer: Los Andrinis (Box 41)
          Disc 1, side 1: Tango Verde / Ricardo Romero, Andalucia / Ernesto Lecuona
          Disc 1, side 2: Tico tico no fuba / Zequinha Abreu, Alma Llanera / Pedro Elias Gutierrez
          Disc 2, side 1: Granada / Augustin Lara, Recuerdos / Jose Moreno
          Disc 2, side 2: 18th de Septiembre / Tomas Moscoso, Sol y Sombra / Ricardo Romero
          Record Label: Alpha Records 12207--12208 (3057--3058)
      - #73 Title: Algo se quema alla afuera (Something is burning out there)
        - Performer: Estrella Artau (Box 41)
          Side 1: Mi nombre es Estrella Artau, Mi machete de madera, La muralla, Cantaliso en un bar, Caminando, Como el viento en movimiento, Algo se quema alla afuera
          Side 2: Poema; Guerillo, guerillera; A ti, Tingo; Si alguien quiere saber cual es mi patria; Hay un pas en el mundo; La preguntita sobre dios, Cancin Puertoriquea, Fragmentos de los versos de Martin Fierro
          Record Label: Paredon, P.-1032
      - #74 Title: Chants d'Espagna et d'Amerique Latine
        - Performer: Carmela, Paco Ibaez (Box 41)
          Side 1: La gran perdida de alhama, Brisas del zulia, A la mar, Camino el indio, Mi nia se fue a la mar, Yo no canto por cantar
          Side 2: Paloma ausente, Los pastores, La jardinera, Sombras, Mama Juanita, Proverbios y cantares, Palida voz
          Record Label: Mosh-Na, MN-10 006
      - #75 Title: Blazing Frontiers
        - Performer: Compaeros (Box 41)
          Side 1: Valparaiso, Freedom for Nicaragua, Cubita, Trojan Horse, We Sing For You
          Side 2: Beautiful Day, Cancin por Nicaragua, First Message, The Immigrants, Compaero
          Record Label: Rebelion Records, ICS-8802
      - #76 Title: Las voces de Amrica Vol. 2
        - Performer: Los Folkloristas (Box 41)
          Side 1: Puales, Vidalita, Las Bogotanas, El condor pasa, El siquisiri, De punta y Taco
          Side 2: Dalia Chinita, Golpe tocuyano, Reza, Los arrieros, La carreta, Juan sin tierra, La caserita
          Record Label: Gamma, GX 01-306
      - #77 Title: Canti al Che
        - Performer: Meri Franco-Lao (Box 41)
          Side 1: El aparecido, Anch'io ti ricordero', Cancin del guerrillero heroico, Aleluia, Si el poeta eres tu, Lorsque s'allument les brasiers, Changuito guerrillero, Como el Che
          Side 2: Addio Che, Soy loco por ti America, Zamba al Che, Guevara morto
          Record Label: I Dischi dello Zodiaco, VPA 8127
      - #78 Title: Chants rvolutionnaires du monde
        - Performer: Groupe "17" (Box 41)
          Side 1 and 2: L'internationale, Les partisans, La varsovienne, Le chant des survivants, Le drapeau rouge, Fleur cueillie..., Hardi, camarades!, Les quatre gnraux, L'appel de komintern, Le chant des marais, La jeune garde, Le chant des martyrs, Le front des travailleurs, Bandiera Rossa, Solidarit
          Record Label: Le Chant du Monde, LDX 74335
      - #79 Title: Songs and Poetry of the Latin American Struggle
        - Performer: El Grupo (Box 41)
          Side 1: Pedro Pueblo; Chile, paloma herida; Te digo hermano, Sigue la vida su curso, Despierta boricua, Superpig
          Side 2: Cancin por la flor y el fusil, Marta Cristina, Cancin con todos, Act of Love, Comunidad
          Record Label: Canto Libre, CL100
      - #80 Title: Himnos de lucha, Fighting Hymns, Hymnes de Lutte (Box 41)
        Side 1: Himno de los campamentos de al fat'h, Himno nacional de Guatemala, Himno de Republica de Guinea
        Side 2: Himno de los constitucionalistas Dominicanos, Himno del Partido Africano de la Independencia de Guinea y Cabo Verde, Himno de la Republica Popular Democratica de Corea
        Record Label: Tricontinental, Himnos Revolucionarios, LD T 1
      - #81 Title: De rebeldes a revolucionarios (Box 42)
        - Performer: Noel Hernandez (Box 42)
          Side 1: Ya se van, Cinco hermanos preso, Al amigo sincero, Contrariedad, Estudiantes y obreros
          Side 2: Guerrillero, guerrillero; Tristes sucesos, Discurso sobre A.L., Se acabo se acabo
          Record Label: Disco Libre, LD-003
      - #82 Title: Inti-illimani (Box 42)
        Side 1: Juanito Laguna remonta un barrilete, El canelazo, Vasija de barro, Sicuriadas, Zamba de los humildes, Cuecas - Largume la manga, El musico errante
        Side 2: La fiesta de San Benito, Simon Bolivar, Jenecheru, La naranja, Inti-illimani, Carta al Che, La lagrima
        Record Label: Jota Jota, JJL-05
      - #83 Title: Canti della libert
        - Performer: Milva (Box 42)
          Side 1: Inno a Oberdan, Addio Lugano bella, Fischia il vento, Los cuatro generales, Horstwessel Lied
          Side 2: La marseillaise, La Carmagnole, Lungo la strada, John Brown, La Cucaracha
          Record Label: Cetra, LPB 35027
      - #84 Title: Canti della resistenza Europea, 1933-1963
        - Performer: Sergio Liberovici, Michele L. Straniero (Box 42)
          Vol. 1, Side 1: Ebrei, Albania, Austria, Belgio, Bulgaria
          Side 2: Cecoslovacchia, Francia, Germania
          Vol. 2, Side 1: Grecia, Jugoslavia
          Side 2: Italia, Polonia, Portogallo
          Vol. 3, Side 1: Romania, Spagna
          Side 2: Ungheria, U.R.S.S.
          Record Label: Discoteca de L'Espresso, GLP 81003--GLP 81005
      - #85 Title: Ogni giorno, tutti i giorni
        - Performer: Sergio Liberovici (Box 42)
          Side 1: Terra e aqua, La morte di Anita, Declaracin, Il padrone del mondo, Le pietre e il mare, Ma cosa ti credi, D'un tratto grid
          Side 2: Ballata del Now, Ante la vita, I will despair, Dove vola l'avvoltoio, Il ginocchio, Hunger is Hunger
          Record Label: I Dischi del Sole, DS 134/36/CL-B
      - #86 Title: Colette Magny
        - Performer: Colette Magny (2 Copies) (Box 42)
          Side 1: Vietnam 67, Aurons-nous point la paix?, Choisis ton opium, Dsembourbez l'avenir, Viva Cuba, Je chanterai, Les gens de la moyenne, La blanche Aminte
          Side 2: La dame du Guerveur, Trois motifs, Bura Bura, A l'origine, Baise m'encor, A Saint-Nazaire
          Record Label: Le Chant du Monde, LDX 74319
      - #87 Title: Misa Panamericana: Grabada en la Catedral de Cuernavaca, Morelos (Box 42)
        Side 1: Entrada Angelus; Seor, ten piedad; Gloria; Aleluya, Credo
        Side 2: Santo, Santo, Santo; Cordero de Dios, Comunion, Salida Aleluya
        Record Label: Discos Aleluya, A-015
      - #88 Title: Le Chant Profond de l'Amerique Latine
        - Performer: Alfredo & Yolando de Robertis & Pedro Serrano (Box 42)
          Side 1: Changuito guerrillero, Erke, Danzante de la ausencia, Danza de sicuris, Kaphuri, Setoconao, Disparada
          Side 2: Condor pasa, Duerme negrito, Danza aztequa, Sieteleguas, Taquili, El buen borincano
          Record Label: Le Chant du Monde, LDX 7 4395
      - #89 Title: Formando un puente, Building Bridges
        - Performer: Saba (Box 42)
          Side 1: La andina, Mis razones, La vieja, Uno ms uno, Madre campesina, Tempestad libertaria
          Side 2: Mujer Sandinista, Basta corazn, No a la intervencin, Cuanto trabajo, Eterna sombra
          Record Label: Redwood Records, RR2900
      - #90 Title: Maderos Latinoamericanos
        - Performer: Julio Solrzano (Box 42)
          Side 1: No me pregunten, Semana santa en Guatemala, Ho Chi Min, Cancin de los ausentes en Tlatelolco, Maderas
          Side 2: Es hora de decir basta, Cancin del esposo soldado, Cancin a nora paz, La tierra humeda, Barricadas
          Record Label: Discos NCL, NCL-LP-001
      - #91 Title: Freedom First
        - Performer: Spartacus R (Box 42)
          Side 1: Freedom First, Black and White Moderate Show, Caterpillar, Oh Mama, Look around you People, Bury my Heart at Wounded Knee
          Side 2: Run with the Living, Live and Let me Live, Too Much, He was my Friend, Friendly Feeling
          Record Label: Zara Music Records, ZMR LP 4
      - #92 Title: Brotando del Silencio (Breaking Out of the Silence)
        - Performer: Suni Paz (Box 42)
          Side 1: Abrele paso a mi fusil, Prisioneros somos, Quiero decirte, Queca del auto; Albizu campos, sembrador; Las condiciones; Tania, guerillera
          Side 2: A mi guerrero, Corrido de Aztlan, Canto a culebra, Indio y negro, La bamba chicana, Canto y amenecer, Hasta la victoria siempre
          Record Label: Paredon, P-1016
      - #93 Title: From the Sky of My Childhood (Del cielo de mi ninez): Folk Songs from Latin America
        - Performer: Suni Paz (Box 42)
          Side 1: Cancin de la ternura, La llorona, Pollerita colorada, Al ajo, Manos vacas, Vamos chamar o vento
          Side 2: Corazn contesta, Por signos, Casi-casi, Cancin por un nio en la calle, Soe que el fuego se helaba, Coplas de la Quebrada de humahuaca
          Record Label: Folkway Records, FW 8875
      - #94 Title: Tropicos: Songs of Cuba and Brazil
        - Performer: Daniel Viglietti with El Grupo de Experimentacion Sonora del Cuba (Box 42)
          Side 1: Dios le pague, Yo vivo en un tiempo de guerra, Acalanto, Upa negrito, Construccin
          Side 2: Comienzo el dia, Existen, Cancin del Elegido, Pobre del cantor, Un hombre se levanta
          Record Label: Monitor Music of the World, MFS 791
    - Greece (Box 43)
      - #95 Title: Chansons de Mikis Theodorakis
        - Performer: Soula Birbili (Box 43)
          Side 1: Marina, To Gelasto Pedi, Agapi Mou, Dakysmena Matia, Apo To Parathyro Sou, O Kipos Ebene Sti Thalassa
          Side 2: Kimissou Angeloudi Mou, Tadate Ta Mathate?, To Psomi Ine Stopi Trapezi, Tou Mikrou Voria, Hathika, Prodomeni Mou Agapi
          Record Label: Le Chant du Monde, LDX-S-4327
      - #96 Title: Chansons de lutte (Songs of Strife) (Box 43)
        Side 1: Aujourd'hui la Grece ( Greece Today), A nikiforos Mandilaras, Les premiers morts, Lorsque tu frapperas a ma porte, Lamentation, N'oublie pas oropos, Pour non obeissance aux instructions, Le Gaillard
        Side 2: Rue Bouboulinas une lettre, La cour, Celui qui me pourchasse, Ferme donc la fenetre, Les volcans, A samos, Les vœux
        Record Label: 2445 004
      - #97 Title: Mauthauzen and Six Songs
        - Performer: Maria Farantouri (Box 43)
          Side 1: Asma Asmaton, O Andonis, O Drapetis, Otan Teliossi O Polemos
          Side 2: Kourastika Na Se Krato, O Iskios Epesse Varis, Pira Tous Dromous T'Ouranou, Stou Kosmu Tin Aniforia, To Ekkremes, T'oneiro Kapnos
          Record Label: Broadside Records, BRS 309
      - #98 Title: The Ballad of a Free People: The Story of the Greeks
        - Performer: Mikis Theodorakis, Yannis Ritsos (Box 43)
          Side 1: Afta ta dentra, Oli Dipsane, Otan sfingoun to cheri, Tossa chronia, Bikan sta sidera
          Side 2: Dendro to dendro, Pios na to pi, Tha simanoun I cambanes, Travixane Psila
          Record Label: Broadside Records, BR 307
      - #99 Title: Etat de Siege, Pome "Marina"
        - Performer: Mikis Theodorakis, Maria Farantouri, Antonis Kaloyannis (Box 43)
          Record Label: Polydor, 184 357
    - Italy
      - #100 Title: Canti di donne in lotta: movimento femminista romano, n. 2 (Box 43)
        Side 1: Felicita', Una donna nella tua vita, Il mestiere piu' antico, Abortire, 8 Marzo, Ma verra' un giorno
        Side 2: Amore, Umanita', Storia di una cosa, Tango della femminista, Frigida, Mi guardo in uno specchio
        Record Label: I Dischi Dello Zodiaco, VPA 8307
      - #101 Title: Canto della resistenza (Box 43)
        Side 1: Inno di mameli, Bella ciao, La' su quei monti, Il bersagliere ha cento penne, Pieta' l'e' morta, Lungo la strada
        Side 2: La stella del partigiano, Cosa rimiri mio bel partigiano, Valsesia, Ma mi, Il canto dei deportati, Non voglio piu'
        Record Label: Las Vegas, LV 3004
      - #102 Title: Chants des migrants italiens (Box 43)
        Side 1: Italia bella, mostrati gentile, Quando saremo en merica, E tutti va in Francia, Vuoi tu venir giuletta?, Sei bella negli occhi, Io parto per l' America, Santa Lucia Luntana, Quando l'albero comincia a fiorire
        Side 2: Il tragico affondamento del bastimento "Sirio", Mamma mia, dammi centro lire, Trenta giorni di nave a vapore, Il tuo ritorno, Fox-trot della nostalgia, La tragedia del Mattmark
        Record Label: Le Chant du Monde, LDX 74477
      - #103 Title: Ivan Della Mea
        - Performer: Ivan Della Mea, Giorgio Gaslini Big Band (Box 43)
          Side 1: Il fiume furore
          Side 2: Canto per i martiri negri
          Record Label: I Dischi del Sole, DS 167/69/CL
      - #104 Title: Io so che un giorno
        - Performer: Ivan Della Mea (Box 43)
          Side 1: Io so che un giorno, Mi so no el perch, Quand riva 'l cald', A quel omm'
          Side 2: Sent' un po', Gioan, te se ricordet; Te se ricordet, Gioan, de me fradel; El diluvi; Che cosa voglion dire gli occhi tristi; Mangia el carbon e tira l'ultim fi
          Record Label: I Dischi del Sole, DS 122/24
      - #105 Title: Il rosso diventato giallo (Red Has Become Yellow)
        - Performer: Ivan Della Mea (Box 43)
          Side 1: Venne maggio: Prologo di un anno, Forza giuan l'idea non morta, Nostro amor la crescer, Domani amore andremo
          Side 2: un buon padre un bravo italiano ma..., A questo punto il prezzo qual', Perch mai parlarci di pace, Il rosso diventato giallo
          Record Label: I Dischi Dello Zodiaco, VPA 8104